mijireh.com 2019-01-04

# Privacy Policy | CloudSwipe

CloudSwipe is a secure hosted payment page service that offers a PCI Compliant and secure credit card payment form that allows you to integrate your e-commerce website with a large number of payment gateways around the world. We value and respect your privacy and will take all reasonable steps to protect your and your customers‚ personal information.

## What does this Privacy Policy apply to?

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to cloudswipe.com, all subpages (together, the Website) and all software and services that we offer through our Website. This Policy does NOT apply to any website, service or product of any third-party even if such third party links to or is linked from our Website. We do not control or operate those websites, services or products and assume no responsibility for them. You should carefully review the privacy policies of such third party websites, services or products before deciding whether to provide any personal information.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information in several ways: (i) when you send us an e-mail or communicate via any other electronic means we will store the address and the conversation history; (ii) when you register via our Website we will collect and store certain personal data that may include your address, phone numbers, credit card numbers, IP address, location, information about your computer or device and other standard web log information; (iii) when a customer uses a checkout process on a merchant, website that is integrated to CloudSwipe, we will gather and may store payment card data, billing details and other personal data required to process the transaction.

We refer to the information we collect generally as “personal information”, which includes any information that can be used to identify an individual or any anonymous information that is linked to a specific individual. Any information that is aggregated or becomes anonymous such that it cannot be reasonably associated with an individual shall not be considered personal information.

### Cookies

We may collect information about your computer (including your IP address), operating system and browser type, for system administration purposes.

We may also obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our Website, deliver a better and more personalized service, look for possible fraudulent activity, and to be better understand the sources of traffic to our Website.

You may elect to refuse acceptance of cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this option you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will automatically issue cookies when you log on to our Website.

### What we do with your information

CloudSwipe uses the collected information for the following general purposes including products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

We may occasionally email you with information about new service offerings. You may opt-out of these emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in such communications. Please note that you will continue to receive communications about your CloudSwipe account including billing invoices and usage notifications.

### How do we share and disclose information?

We are not allowed to disclose personal information without your written permission and will never sell or rent your personal information to marketers.

Certain information collected about you and your customers is used within the context of providing CloudSwipe services. We may store personal information with third parties in locations outside our direct control, for example on offsite servers or databases. By signing up for a CloudSwipe account you acknowledge that we may share payment transaction data and related information with third parties to the extent necessary to process transactions via the CloudSwipe service. The use of personal information by such third party will be subject to their applicable privacy policy, which we recommend you carefully review.

In certain circumstances we may be required to disclose personal information to government officials, law enforcement or other third parties: (i) in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the CloudSwipe terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; (ii) if we are compelled to do so by subpoena, court order or other legal process; or (iii) if we are required to do so to comply with any law, statute, or set of rules or regulations.

We will only disclose personal information in response to a request if we believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with any applicable law or legal requirement. We will use reasonable efforts to provide you prompt notice prior to such disclosure so that you can contest the requirement if you choose unless we determine in good faith that: (i) we are not permitted to provide you such notice under any applicable law; or (ii) giving such notice would result in an imminent risk of death, serious injury or significant property loss or damage to CloudSwipe or a third party.

In the event CloudSwipe is acquired by or merged with another company or enters into a reorganization, bankruptcy or any other similar event then we may also transfer any personal information to our successor assign. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Website before any personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Security and protection of information

The security of your personal information is extremely important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as a credit card number on our registration form, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. CloudSwipe maintains strict administrative technical, and physical procedures to protect information stored by the service. All servers are are located in the United States, and access to personal information is limited. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can send email us at support@cloudswipe.com.

### Client Data Storage

CloudSwipe owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the CloudSwipe application, but we make no claim to the rights of your data. You retain all rights to your data and we will never contact your clients directly, or use your data for our own business advantage or to compete with you or market to your clients.

You can request to have your personal information deleted at any time.  This includes both your information as well as information about the customers who have interacted with your CloudSwipe account to pay for invoices.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it occasionally to ensure you’re still in agreement with its provisions. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our Website so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You agree that electronic disclosures and notices have the same meaning and effect as if we had provided you with a paper copy.

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to support@cloudswipe.com.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018_
